tableplus.com 2019-12-02

# TablePlus | Modern, Native Tool for Database Management

TablePlus Inc. ("we" or "us") values our customers and respects their privacy. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which we collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the TablePlus website ("Site") and TablePlus applications (“Apps”).

SECTION 1 - COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

A. When you use the Apps.

We use a one-way private hash to identify your device for the licensing management and it does not contain any personal information about your device.

We collect crash report and this information is anonymous, non-personal behavioural data. However, you can opt out by turning off the Crash Report from the Apps’ preferences setting.

B. When you use the Site.

We automatically collect certain kinds of non-personal information from you when you use the Site, including device, browser type, operating system, referring or exit web pages, click patterns, Session ID, your computer's IP address, and some other browser-based information.

We may collect the Personal Information you give us when you purchase the license, including email address, credit card or bank information, and other Personal Information requested as part of your purchase.

SECTION 2 - HOW YOUR INFORMATION IS USED

Except as provided herein, we collect and use your personal and non-personal information for internal purposes only or for gathering aggregate and anonymized data, and we do not sell, rent, or share personally identifiable information about you with other people or with nonaffiliated companies except as described below. We may use your information in the following ways:

To conduct routine business operations such as billing, identification, authentication, contact purposes and general research. As part of our routine business operations, we may transfer your Personal Information to certain third parties with whom we contract for the limited purpose of providing services such as web hosting, email, and credit card processing. These service providers are obligated to protect your information, and they do not use your Personal Information for their own commercial purposes.

To communicate with you about important announcements, special offers and support.

To provide you with and enhance the Services.

To gather generic product, location and other contributed information to make reports based on aggregate anonymized data, which we may use internally, or which we may share with others for a variety of purposes, including for their own uses.

To comply with court and governmental orders.

YOUR USER CONTENT

Your User Content will be treated as follows:

The Apps connect you directly to your database without making any interferences. The connection is end-to-end encrypted.

Queries you make using the Apps are only accessible by you.

We never sync or send your database credentials, queries, history, favorite or any of your database content to any of our servers. The credentials are always being saved securely on your device's hard drive.

SECTION 3 - CONSENT

When you provide us with your information to use the Site or the Apps, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

SECTION 4 - DISCLOSURE

We will not share your Personal Information with third parties without your express consent, except in the limited circumstances described below:

We may share your Personal Information with third party service providers for the limited purposes described in the section entitled "How Your Information is Used."

We will share your Personal Information when required by law, regulation, or litigation, and as necessary for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance.

If we sell assets or are acquired by or merged with another entity, we may provide such entity customer information without obtaining your further consent. We may provide notice of such asset sales, acquisitions, or mergers on the Site.

SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

SECTION 6 - SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

COOKIES

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

SECTION 7 - AGE OF CONSENT

The Site and the Apps are intended for adult audiences only, and we do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from anyone under 13 years of age. If you are under age 13, please do not provide any Personal Information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately.

SECTION 8 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If we sell assets or are acquired by or merged with another entity, we may provide such entity customer information without obtaining your further consent. We may provide notice of such asset sales, acquisitions, or mergers on the Site.

QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
